1.  The most basic requirement is that the computer always chooses a legal move：

My Answer:
I use a check_legal_move() function to control legal move:
When the check_legal_move() function return True, it means there is at least one position to legal move.
When the check_legal_move() function return False, it means there is no legal move.

2.Did you attempt to make your computer player very smart -- i.e., do something more clever than just pick a random legal move?

My Answer:
I make a get_computer_draw_pos() function. The function is doing:

(1) Check all legal move position for computer, for each legal position, it will return a number of how many tiles it can flip
if this legal position is drawing a tile.
(2) compare all numbers and pick the biggest number. 
(3) Return the postion which made that number, for example:
   if the position (3,4) which means row 3 column 4 is legal move for computer, and after draw at there, computer can gain 
   20 enemy tils, which is the most among all legal position, then this function return (3,4)

By applying this function to my AI computer, it will draw at the legal move which can get most enemy tiles on that round.

3.If so, were you able to accomplish this? Is your computer player as smart as you would like?
My answer: I accomplish it. Computer play is kind of as smart as I would like, but not enough.

4.How did you determine which piece to play next?  Tell us about your “pick next move” algorithm.
My answer: See answer for Question 2

5.How often did your computer program beat you, or your friends, or whoever tested it out for you?
My answer: At the begining computer beat me and my friend a lot. But as we playing better using our human algorithm
(which I will write in the next question) we beat it more.

6.How would you improve it in the future? 
My answer:
I find that, in this game, the very corner position is most important for the finally winning. And positions around it is also important.
So in the future I want to add a condition to AI, such as the corner and position around it have higher priority to draw when it is in legal moves.



